Hi everyone and welcome to this lingerie try on video and I'm super happy that I can present a
US-based store today. I know that a lot of you are from the US or Canada so I'm teamed up with
adamandeve.com and I'm going to show you I think six, seven, seven or eight outfits today and I
I also have a discount code, my name, Celine, for 50% off of one item and free shipping in the US and Canada.
I of course link everything down below.
I'm super excited about the first outfit because it's a cosplay, schoolgirl, lingerie, whatever outfit you'll see for yourself in a sec.
First outfit, one piece is still missing. There's also a collar and a tie.
Now it's complete. It's called Slytherin and I think I know what this refers to so I got my wand.
And to follow up the ultimate Skooga look, here are my glasses.
Although I'm not a Slytherin, but there was only this colour option.
But I think it's really really cute, also with the matching briefs and the fluffy skirt.
I think it's totally adorable.
Yeah, I definitely like this look.
And I paired it with some over-knee boots
to give it more of this
I don't know, Nordkies schoolgirl vibe.
I've never done something like this, so I was like
I'm going to order that one.
I want to see how this looks.
And yeah,
do you like it? Tell me in the comments
if
you like this look.
grown on me. I think it's super fun and I think this is the most playful outfit.
The other ones are more like one-piece outfits so this is like one two three
four five pieces and it's a standard size small medium and it does fit okay.
so I'm really happy with this choice and now I'm going to use a spell to get me
into the next outfit second outfit and I have to say I love it it looks really
good and it also fits really good so it's kind of a wet look fabric and lots
of rivets. It's rather heavy because of all the metal parts and yeah, it's nice. It's
adjustable here in the neck so I wear it a bit more loose around the neck so there's
not too much tension going on here. Anyway, I think it fits really good. Nice! Okay, so
Both of the outfits I tried so far are really cool.
I have two favorites now.
I think you can't really compare them to each other.
Because it's a completely different look.
And I also have some other more lacy stuff showing you next.
But first I think I have to take some pictures with this one.
My first baby doll ever.
It also comes with a matching panty.
and I never wore baby dolls because I always thought in the past that they
make me look like pregnant but I have to say it doesn't in this case so it's
see-through and nice and frilly and I quite like it I'm surprised because as I
said never thought I would like to wear baby doll lingerie maybe I should get
more of them it's like a dress and bra in combination I don't know also maybe
to yeah where is pyjama is this an option I don't know but I can say that
I'm pleasantly surprised and I also really like the color so it's a really
nice purple and with the black bra part here it's cool to wear matching black
heels so third outfit that I like so far you have really really good count I
picked size medium for this one because I read that it runs small and I also
check the measurement table but I think a S would fit as well. Alright Valentine's
Day is over but hey I mean maybe an idea for next year because there are little hearts
here. Oh it's so cute there's also a heart in the back. So these are two separate
pieces this morning gown and the lingerie set I matched them together because they're both red
and I thought well maybe it looks good it does look good I think I did not have nude stockings
so I'm going with the black ones but I really like the lingerie three-piece set and also the
morning gown. There are a lot of bows and also hearts here. It's so cute. It's not my usual type
of lingerie and I think this is again size small medium. It runs a bit small I would say so
it's a bit tight somewhere but I love how the garter belt completes the whole outfit. I think
The piranha panty wouldn't look as good together as they do with the belt here
Pulls the outfit really together
after all the colors
Let's do the last black outfit
It's a bodysuit. Oh, I don't know. I think they call it Teddy never heard of the term Teddy for
Like a bodysuit like that. It's basically just lace
and you can make a knot in the back of the neck so it's kind of size adjustable
and you can see a lot so yeah I'm going to change to the next outfit oh and by the
way I'm wearing pasties underneath the stars so I'm not showing too much in
this video. Last outfit for today it's called a teddy doll. So it's a combination of
teddy, a bodysuit and a baby doll and I love the idea. I mean you don't show too
much because you have the see-through fabric here but it's also really
playful and has nice details like these straps here the lazy parts so I like it
never heard of this combination or saw it before but what can I say it's fun
and I also like the color it's size medium but I think it fits a bit better
than the other baby doll so it's a bit smaller small medium and I totally like
the look also that the skirt part here runs like a V in the back cute what do
you think of this video for today because it is a bit different than my
normal videos also the colors and the designs but I like them very much I
discovered a lot of new things today. Things I didn't know I like. So check out adamandeve.com
and leave a comment down below. Also give a thumbs up to this video and see you in the next video. Bye!